ollies.us 2018-08-31

# Privacy Policy - Store Policies | Ollie's Bargain Outlet

### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") applies to your use of the Ollie's Bargain Outlet, Inc. (referred to herein as "we," "us," or "our") website or mobile application (collectively the "Sites"). The purpose of our privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") is to inform you about the types of personally identifiable information we gather about you when you visit our Sites, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct the information.  The phrases "personally identifiable information" or "personal information" mean any information by which you can be identified, such as your name, address, telephone number.  Please read our complete Privacy Policy.  By using our Sites, you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, which is part of, and governed by our Terms of Use _[[http://www.ollies.us/store-policies/terms-of-use/]](http://www.ollies.us/store-policies/terms-of-use/)_.  Whenever you submit information via our Sites, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use, please do not use our Sites or submit information to us.

### Information Collection

As you navigate through our Sites, certain information can be passively collected using various technologies, such as navigational data collection.  We, or third parties authorized by us, may transparently collect information that is not personally-identifiable about your online activities over time and across different web sites when you use our Site, such as what browser is being used (e.g., Internet Explorer), the operating system of the device you use to access our Sites or the domain name from which you entered a site (e.g., google.com), your internet protocol address, your interactions with our Site and the amount of time you spend; however, this information is used for our internal purposes only. We do not control what information third parties collect about you when you navigate their sites including when you move from third-party sites to our Sites. 

Our Sites may use "cookies."  A "cookie" is a small file stored by your Web browser to help a particular system recognize you and the pages you visit in our Sites.  Cookies allow our Sites to recognize you more quickly and provide a customized user experience.  We use cookies to help us measure the number of visits, average time spent, page views, and other statistics relating to our Sites.  The information we gather through the use of cookies is not sold to vendors, advertisers, direct mail concerns, or email list services.  If you disable cookies, certain functions of our Sites may not work properly or be available to you.

We may use third party analytical applications to analyze our Sites traffic and collect non personally identifiable information about the use of our Sites by individual users and users in the aggregate.  We do not change our information-collection practices or use of cookies based on the do not track settings in your browser. 

### Third Party Websites

Our Sites may contain links to other websites including those that permit online transactions.  We have no control over the privacy practices or the content of any of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide links from our Sites.  We do not endorse, approve or certify these other websites, and we do not guarantee the accuracy, completeness, efficacy, or timeliness of the information contained on these sites.  This Privacy Policy applies to information collected by our Sites, and you should check the applicable privacy policy of the website sponsor when linking to other websites.

### Information You Submit **  **

As a visitor to our Sites you can be assured that at no time will we collect personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide that information to us as described in the next section.  We respect your privacy online and will never share any of your personal information with third parties.

The only exception to the collection of personal information is when you specifically and knowingly provide your contact information to us when communicating with us via our online form to request information, to update your Ollie’s Army member information, or to be contacted by Ollie’s.  Any information provided by you through our online form is used solely for the purpose provided.

While we are the sole owner of all information collected on our Sites, as we develop our business we may sell our business or buy another business.  In such transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferred business assets.  In the event that we or substantially all of our assets are acquired, personal information about our customers may be one of the transferred assets.

We will also disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on us; (b) protect and defend our rights or property; (c) comply with a written request from a law enforcement agency if the information requested to assist that agency with the investigation/prosecution of a crime; or (d) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of our Sites or the public.

We will not use your personal information in a way that is incompatible with these stated purposes, unless we obtain your prior consent.

### Security and Your Account

We will take reasonable steps to protect your personally identifiable information that you transmit to us from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.  However, no Internet transmission is ever fully secure, and we cannot guarantee that information transmitted via our Sites will remain uncompromised and confidential at all times.  When we collect other information from our users, it is stored in an area to which the general public does not have access.  We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to ensure that personal information is stored and treated responsibly. No system of protection is perfect, however, and unauthorized third parties may attempt to gain access, or actually gain access to this area of our computer network.

In the event that any use of any aspect of our Sites involves log-in credentials, please bear in mind that anyone you provide with your log-in information will also have access to your account and personally identifiable information.  If you use our Sites you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any log-in credentials associated with the Sites.

### Children (Under the Age of 13)

We protect children's privacy seriously. We do not seek to collect personal information about children through our Sites. If we become aware that a person submitting information to us through any part of our Sites is a child, we delete the information as soon as we discover it and do not use it for any purpose, nor do we disclose it to third parties. Since we do not seek to collect any personal information about children, and we delete information collected inadvertently as soon as we discover that a child has submitted it, we typically retain no information about children that could be reviewed or deleted. If a parent requests review or deletion of information about their child before we have discovered and deleted the information, we will of course honor that request.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions on our Sites and you agree to any such changes upon your continued use of our Sites.  When changes are made, we will update the effective date of this Policy. This Privacy Policy is not intended to, and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

Effective Date: August 28, 2018
